Arch Oboler Collection
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Series 9. Scripts, 1933-1993 and undated, 70 linear feet (168 boxes)
  - Radio, 1933-1981 and undated
    - "Last Act"
      - Fire file, 1937 July (Box 238, Folder 12)
      - Town file, 1937 July (Box 238, Folder 13)
    - "Last Flight"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 238, Folder 14)
      - Town file, undated (Box 238, Folder 15)
    - "The Last in the World"
      - Fire file, 1942 May (Box 238, Folder 16)
      - Town file, 1942 May (Box 238, Folder 17)
    - "The Last Lesson"
      - Fire file, circa 1939 (Box 238, Folder 18)
      - Town file, circa 1939 (Box 238, Folder 19)
    - "The Last Man in the World" See "Last Woman in the World" (Box 238, Folder 20)
    - "The Last Survivor"
      - Fire file, 1935 March (Box 238, Folder 21)
      - Town file, 1935 March (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - "The Last War"
      - Fire file, 1936 September (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1936 September (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - "The Last Will"
      - Fire file, 1936 April (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1936 April (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - "Last Woman in the World"
      - Fire file, circa 1941 (Box 239, Folder 6)
      - Town file, circa 1941 (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - "The Last Word," fire file, undated (Box 239, Folder 8)
    - "The Laughing Man"
      - Fire file, 1939 April, June, August, 1940 January, 1941 January (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1939 April, 1939 June, 1940 January, 1941 January (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - "The Laughter"
      - Fire file, 1942 November, 1944 June (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1942 November, 1944 June (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - "Legal Aid Society" script See "Wanted: A Lawyer" (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - "Letter at Midnight"
      - Fire file, 1942 January, 1942 March (Box 240, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1942 January, 1942 March (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - "Letter from the Congo"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Town file, undated (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - "Lieutenant Patience"
      - Fire file, 1942 June (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1942 June (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Lights Out
      - Information filed in "ranch" files, 1936-1947 (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous file, 1938 March (Box 241, Folder 6)
      - Stage unit, fire file, undated (Box 241, Folder 7)
      - Stage unit, town file, undated (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - "The Listener"
      - Fire file, 1941 March (Box 241, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1941 March (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - "Little Ireland"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 241, Folder 11)
      - Town file, undated (Box 241, Folder 12)
    - "Little Old Lady"
      - Fire file, 1937 November, 1943 May (Box 241, Folder 13)
      - Town file, 1937 November, 1943 May (Box 241, Folder 14)
    - "The Little People"
      - Fire file, 1937 April, 1943 July (Box 241, Folder 15)
      - Town file, 1937 April, 1943 July (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - "The Little Yellow Basket," fire and town files, circa 1938 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - "Lo, the Poor Indian"
      - Fire file, 1937 November (Box 242, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1937 November (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - "London Ghost Story," CBS Radio pilot, 1980 (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - "Lord Marley's Guest"
      - Fire file, 1937 July, 1943 September (Box 242, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1937 July, 1943 September (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - "Lost Horizon"
      - Fire file, 1944 February (Box 242, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1944 February (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - "Love," fire file, circa 1944-1946 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - "Love Affair" See "Love Story, Ltd." (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - "Love, Love, Love"
      - Fire file, 1945 May (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1944 June, 1945 May, 1949 October (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - "Love Me, Love Nero"
      - Fire file, 1937 April (Box 243, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1937 April (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - "Love on Ice"
      - Fire file, 1936 February (Box 243, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1936 February (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - "Love 100%"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - Town file, undated (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - "Love Story, Ltd."
      - Fire file, 1939 September, 1941 May (Box 244, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1939 September (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - "Love Story" series
      - Fire file, 1943 September (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1943 September (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - "The Lover"
      - Fire file, circa 1949-circa 1951 (Box 244, Folder 7)
      - Town file, undated (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - "Luck," fire file, undated (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - "The Luck of Mark Street"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 244, Folder 10)
      - Town file, undated (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - "Lucky Lady"
      - Fire file, circa 1939 (Box 244, Folder 12)
      - Town file, undated (Box 244, Folder 13)
    - "Lust for Life"
      - Fire file, 1945 April, 1945 August (Box 245, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1945 April, 1945 August (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - "The Machine"
      - Fire file, 1939 October (Box 245, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1939 October (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - "Mad World"
      - Fire file, 1937 May (Box 245, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1937 May (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - "Madame Affamee"
      - Fire file, 1941 January (Box 245, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1941 January (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - "Mademoiselle Detective"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 245, Folder 9)
      - Town file, undated (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - "Mail-Box Romance"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 245, Folder 11)
      - Town file, undated (Box 245, Folder 12)
    - "Mama's Little Quarterback"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 246, Folder 1)
      - Town file, undated (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - "A Man — A Woman and a Man," fire and town files, 1939 June (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - "Man of the House," town file, undated (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - "Man Test"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 246, Folder 5)
      - Town file, undated (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - "The Man to Hate"
      - Fire file, 1939 August (Box 246, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1939 August (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - "A Man to Remember"
      - Fire file, 1944 February (Box 246, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1944 February (Box 246, Folder 10)
    - "Man Who Murdered Himself," fire and town files, circa 1943 (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - "March of Dimes 1942" See "Hollywood's March of Dimes of the Air" (Box 246, Folder 12)
    - "March of Dimes 1945" See "Wonderful World" (Box 246, Folder 12)
    - "Margin for Error"
      - Fire file, circa 1941 (Box 246, Folder 13)
      - Town file, 1941 September (Box 246, Folder 14)
    - "Mark Twain on Life"
      - Fire file, 1944 January (Box 246, Folder 15)
      - Town file, 1944 January (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - "Mark Twain's Legacy"
      - Fire file, 1944 February (Box 247, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1944 February (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - "Mark Twain's Love Story"
      - Fire file, 1944 January (Box 247, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1944 January (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - "Marriage in Heaven"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 247, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1937 April (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - "Marriage 1942"
      - Fire file, 1942 January, November (Box 247, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1942 January, November (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - "Mary's Lamb"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 247, Folder 10)
      - Town file, undated (Box 247, Folder 11)
    - "Masquerade"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 247, Folder 12)
      - Town file, undated (Box 247, Folder 13)
    - "Meet the Champ"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 247, Folder 14)
      - Town file, undated (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - "Memo to Berchtgesgaden"
      - Fire file, 1942 February (Box 248, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1942 February (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - "Memoriam"
      - Fire file, 1939 April, 1940 February (Box 248, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1939 April, 1940 February (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - "Men of Briant"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 248, Folder 6)
      - Town file, undated (Box 248, Folder 7)
    - "Meteor Man," fire and town files, 1942 December (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - "Midnight Flight"
      - Fire file, 1937 July (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1937 July (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - "Millionaires Only"
      - Fire file, 1935 June (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1935 June (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - "Millions for Defense," fire and town files, 1941 July (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - "Miracle in 3B"
      - Fire file, 1942 April-1944 June (Box 249, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1942 April-1944 June (Box 249, Folder 8)
    - "Mirage"
      - Fire file, 1939 October, 1939 April, November, 1943 September (Box 249, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1939 April, November, 1943 September, 1964 January (Box 250, Folder 1-3)
    - "The Mirror"
      - Fire file, 1940 December, 1943 January (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1940 December, 1943 January (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - "Miss American" See "Suffer Little Children" (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - "Miss Brat"
      - Fire file, 1937 September (Box 250, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1937 September (Box 250, Folder 8)
    - "Miss Crazy"
      - Fire file, 1938 May (Box 250, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1938 May (Box 250, Folder 10)
    - "Miss Drummer"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 250, Folder 11)
      - Town file, undated (Box 250, Folder 12)
    - "Miss Microphone," fire and town files, undated (Box 251, Folder 1-2)
    - "Miss T.N.T."
      - Fire file, 1936 October (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1936 October (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - "Mrs. Eve"
      - Fire file, 1937 December (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1937 December (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - "Mr. And Mrs. Robin Hood," fire and town files, undated (Box 251, Folder 7)
    - "Mr. Fiction"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 251, Folder 8)
      - Town file, undated (Box 251, Folder 9)
    - "Mr. Ginsburg"
      - Fire file, 1939 January, 1940 January, 1941 February, 1945 October (Box 251, Folder 10)
      - Town file, 1940 January (Box 251, Folder 11)
    - Mr. Ginsburg, or Mr. Miller, town file, 1939 January, 1940 January, 1941 February (Box 251, Folder 12)
    - "Mr. Important"
      - Fire file, 1939 April (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1939 April (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - "Mr. Larry"
      - Fire file, 1939 June-July (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1939 July (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - "Mr. Maggs"
      - Fire file, 1942 December (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1942 November-December (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - "Mr. Miller," town file, 1945 October, 1963 May (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - "Mr. Pip"
      - Fire file, 1939 December, 1941 January (Box 252, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1939 December, 1941 January, 1949 October (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - "Mr. Pyle"
      - Fire file, 1945 June (Box 252, Folder 10)
      - Town file, 1945 June (Box 252, Folder 11)
    - "Mr. Right"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 252, Folder 12)
      - Town file, 1936 August (Box 252, Folder 13)
    - "Mr. Ten Percent"
      - Fire file, 1945 May-June (Box 252, Folder 14)
      - Town file, 1945 May, 1951 February (Box 252, Folder 15)
    - "Mr. Tutt," fire and town files, 1938 February (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - "Mr. Whiskers"
      - Fire file, 1939 September, 1940 December (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1939 September, 1940 December (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - "Mister Yes 'n' No"
      - Fire file, 1935 September (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1935 September, circa 1964 (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - "Money, Money, Money"
      - Fire file, 1940 January, 1943 March (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1940 January, 1943 March, circa 1964 (Box 254, Folder 2-3)
    - "Monte Carlo Interlude"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Town file, undated (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - "Moon Crazy," fire and town files, 1941 June (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - "The Morbid Mr. Murphy"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 254, Folder 7)
      - Town file, undated (Box 254, Folder 8)
    - "Morning and Night," introductions for Ted Cott, fire and town files, undated (Box 254, Folder 9)
    - "The Most Dangerous Game"
      - Fire file, 1940 March (Box 254, Folder 10)
      - Town file, 1940 March (Box 254, Folder 11)
    - "Mother-in-Law", Oboler retitled this 1938 episode of Lights Out as "Knock at the Door" for a 1942 broadcast.
      - Fire file, 1938 March, 1942 December (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1938 March, 1942 December (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - "Mungahra"
      - Fire file, 1936 November, 1939 September, 1942 October (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1936 November, 1939 September, 1942 October (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - "Murder Below"
      - Fire file, 1936 December (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1936 December (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - "Murder Castle"
      - Fire file, 1938 February, 1943 August (Box 255, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1938 February, 1943 August (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - "Murder in the Script Department"
      - Fire file, 1943 May (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1943 May (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - "Murder on Display," town file, undated (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - "Music on the Mississippi"
      - Fire file, 1944 January (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1944 January (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - "The Musical Mr. Mulligan"
      - Fire file, 1935 August (Box 256, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1935 August (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - Mutual Radio Theater
      Begun in 1979 as The Sears Radio Theater on CBS, the series was broadcast on Mutual from March until December, 1980. Oboler wrote, produced, and directed a number of the shows.
      - Drafts, as broadcast, actor and actress information, 1980 (Box 256, Folder 9)
      - "House on Fire," 1980 (Box 256, Folder 10-11)
      - "Lion Hunt," 1980 (Box 257, Folder 1-2)
      - "Night," 1980 (Box 257, Folder 3-4)
      - "Vicious Circle," 1980, (1 folder) (Box 257-258, Box 257, Box 258)
      - "What the Devil," 1980 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - "My Beloved Relatives"
      - Fire file, 1942 December (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1942 December (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - "My Chicago"
      - Fire file, 1945 July (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1945 July (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - "The Naked Man"
      - Fire file, 1949 September (Box 258, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1949 September, 1957, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 258-259, Box 258, Box 259)
    - "The Naked Mountain"
      - Fire file, 1945 June (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1945 June (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - "Names on the Land," fire file, 1945 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - "Nature Study"
      - Fire file, 1943 June (Box 259, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1943 June (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - "Nero's Wife"
      - Fire file, 1937 September, 1939 June (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1937 September, 1939 June, circa 1964 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - "Never Leave Me," fire and town files, 1943 September, 1944 January (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - New radio series, fire and town files, undated (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - "New Walls of China"
      - Fire file, 1940 October (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1940 October (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - "New World"
      - Fire file, 1939 December (Box 260, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1939 December (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - "New York Story" See "Reno Story" (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - "Night"
      - Fire file, 1945 June (Box 260, Folder 10)
      - Modern version, fire file, 1945 June (Box 260, Folder 11)
    - "Night Flight"
      - Fire file, 1943 April (Box 260, Folder 12)
      - Town file, 1943 April (Box 260, Folder 13)
    - "Night of Storm"
      - Fire file, 1937 November (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1937 November (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - "Night on the Mountain"
      - Fire file, 1938 April (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1938 April (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Night Wind series, fire and town files, 1938 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - "Ninety Cents"
      - Fire file, 1940 October-November (Box 261, Folder 6)
      - Town file, circa 1940 October (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - "The Ninth Life"
      - Fire file, 1937 April (Box 261, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1937 April (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - "Nobody Died"
      - Fire file, 1936 December, 1939 December (Box 261, Folder 10)
      - Town file, 1936 December, 1939 December (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - "Nothing Ever Happens"
      - Fire file, 1935 July (Box 261, Folder 12)
      - Town file, 1935 July (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - Novel, fire file, 1941 April, November (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - O'Connor tapes, 1976-1978 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      Possibly radio demos.
    - "Of Human Bondage"
      - Fire file, 1941 January, 1944 March (Box 262, Folder 2-3)
      - Town file, 1941 January, 1944 March (Box 262, Folder 4-5)
    - "Oh, Elmer!"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 262, Folder 6)
      - Town file, undated (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - "The Old Boy"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 262, Folder 8)
      - CBS Radio and Omni correspondence, 1979 (Box 262, Folder 9)
      - Sears Radio Theater, "The Mystery Show," 1979 April (Box 263, Folder 1-3)
      - Sears Radio Theater correspondence and award nomination form, 1979-1980 (Box 263, Folder 4)
      - Rewrite for Omni, circa 1979 (Box 263, Folder 5)
      - San Diego State College, town file, undated (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - "Old Cronies," fire and town files, circa 1943 July (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - "One Hour of Glory"
      - Fire file, 1940 January, 1941 October-November (Box 263, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1940 January, 1941 October-November (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - "One Hundred Grand"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 263, Folder 10)
      - Town file, undated (Box 263, Folder 11)
    - One line summaries, undated (Box 263, Folder 12)
      These may be related to radio or television.
    - "One Round Murphy"
      - Fire file, 1937 July, October (Box 264, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1937 October (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - "One Strange Night"
      - Fire file, 1936 February (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1936 February (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - "One Summer Afternoon" See "Afternoon Adventure" (Box 264, Folder 5-6)
    - "One Trip Abroad"
      A story by F. Scott Fitzgerald that was published in the Saturday Evening Post in 1930.
      - For Shriner radio, undated (Box 264, Folder 7)
      - Radio adaptation by Arch Oboler, undated (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - "One Way Ride"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 264, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1937 May (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - "Organ"
      - Fire file, 1937 May, 1943 June (Box 264, Folder 11)
      - Town file, 1943 June (Box 264, Folder 12)
    - "Ostrich in Bed"
      - Fire file, 1944 March (Box 264, Folder 13)
      - Town file, 1944 March, 1949 September (Box 264, Folder 14)
    - "The Other Man"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 265, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1936 December (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Our Aunt Aggie series, fire and town files, 1936 March (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Our Kind of Folks series, fire and town files, 1939 August (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - "Oxychloride X"
      - Fire file, 1938 January, 1943 February (Box 265, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1938 January (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - "Papa Deeds" See "Papa Jonathan" (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - "Papa Jonathan"
      - Fire file, 1938 January, 1939 February, 1941 January, 1944 March (Box 265, Folder 8-9)
      - Town file, 1938 January (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - "Papa Says No"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 265, Folder 11)
      - Town file, undated (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - "Parade (V-Day)"
      - Fire file, 1945 August (Box 265, Folder 13)
      - Town file, 1945 August (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - "Paul"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 266, Folder 2)
      - Town file, undated (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - "Paul Reverski"
      - Fire file, 1942 February (Box 266, Folder 4)
      - Town file, undated (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - "Pay the Piper"
      - Fire file, 1941 September, 1942 January (Box 266, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1941 September, 1942 January (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - "The Peacock Shrieks"
      - Fire file, 1936 July (Box 266, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1936 July (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - "The Pearls"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 266, Folder 10)
      - Town file, undated (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - "The People March"
      - Fire file, 1943 February, September (Box 267, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1936 February, September (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - "The Perfect Party"
      - Fire file, 1936 October, 1939 October (Box 267, Folder 3-4)
      - Town file, 1936 October, 1939 October (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - "Perfectly Adorable"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 267, Folder 6)
      - Town file, undated (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - "Petrified Forest"
      - Fire file, 1944 January (Box 268, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1944 January (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - "Point of a Gun"
      - Fire file, 1941 August (Box 268, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1941 August (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - "Poison Pen"
      - Fire file, circa 1939 (Box 268, Folder 5)
      - Town file, circa 1939 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - "Poltergeist," fire and town files, 1942 October (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - "Prelude to Murder"
      - Fire file, 1936 July, 1943 June (Box 268, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1936 July, 1943 June (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - "Problem Papa"
      - Fire file, 1941 March (Box 269, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1941 March (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - "The Producer and the Thing"
      - Fire file, 1943 August-September (Box 269, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1943 September (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - "Professor X" See "Across the Gap" (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - "Profits Unlimited"
      - Fire file, 1939 October, 1941 May, 1943 July (Box 269, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1939 October, 1943 July (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - "The Projective Mr. Drogan"
      - Fire file, 1943 January (Box 269, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1943 January (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - "Psychology, Ltd." See "Love Story, Ltd." (Box 269, Folder 10)
    - "Pyramid"
      - Fire file, 1937 October (Box 270, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1937 October (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - "Quality Street"
      - Fire file, 1944 May (Box 270, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1944 May (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - "Race Track"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 270, Folder 5)
      - Town file, undated (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - "Rancho Pancho"
      - Fire file, 1946 February-March (Box 270, Folder 7)
      - Town file, undated (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Recorded introductions, assorted radio plays, undated (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - "Red Cross Roll Call"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 270, Folder 10)
      - Town file, undated (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - "Refugee," fire file, 1944 November (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - "Reno Story"
      - Fire file, 1934 October (Box 270, Folder 13)
      - Town file, undated (Box 270, Folder 14)
    - "Report to My Relatives," town file, 1945 May (Box 270, Folder 15)
    - "Reunion in Vienna"
      - Fire file, 1944 June (Box 271, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1944 June (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - "Revolt of the Worms"
      - Fire file, 1942 October, 1964 (Box 271, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1942 October, 1964 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - "Rich Kid"
      - Fire file, 1937, 1939 August (Box 271, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1939 August (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - "Rich Woman, Poor Woman"
      - Fire file, 1935 September (Box 271, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1963 October (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - "Rip Von Dinkle"
      - Fire file, 1943 March (Box 271, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1943 March (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - "Rocket from Manhattan"
      - Fire file, 1945 September, 1964 (Box 271, Folder 11)
      - Town file, 1945 September, 1964 January (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - "Rogue Male"
      - Fire file, 1944 February (Box 272, Folder 2)